# Steven Bi

### **Full-Stack Developer**

Perth WA 6107 steven.bb.0221@gmail.com +61 450 980 608

Qualified software engineer, experiences in coding Js, Python and core Java, passionate about web app development with React/Django ecosystem, good on web based data visualization and API development. Familiar with Docker, Git dev environment as well as knowledge of deploy to AWS/GCP.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

#### Personal Details

Eligible to work in Australia: Yes

Highest Level of Education: Bachelor Degree

## Work Experience

#### **Software Developer**

Atomorphis - Perth WA November 2020 to Present

Working on a primary in house product 'Gemini' which is an agent based simulation for helping to identify bottlenecks and plan in mining project , as well as maintain other exist products such as excel & python based data modeling tool.

- Implement Gemini front-end system (React) from scratch, including interactive geological map base
- Finished & delivered a fully functional Gemini prototype for demo.
- Continuously work on Gemini data visualization of mining fleet and equipment simulation in 2D & 3D animation, onsite / underground.
- API development (FastApi)
- Dockerize and maintain whole front-end sytem in docker container

#### Web developer

South Pacific Union Group - Bunbury WA February 2020 to May 2020

Short contract with a local chain hotel in Bunbury, resolve current hotel website issues as well as maintain IT devices.

• Restore website from the damaged backup & online booking system (Wordpress)

- Excel based data summary tool (Python & Pyxl)
- offlline mail marketing system (Python)

### **Software Developer**

Lianjia (https://sh.lianjia.com/) - Shang Hai March 2019 to October 2019

- Maintain current web app backend (Python & Django)
- Improve UI user experience (Materal UI & Js and React)
- Develop & maintain new features

#### **BI Developer**

PinYi Information & Technology Co., Ltd (http://www.shpy.com) - Shang Hai June 2010 to April 2012

- 6 months intership, including knowledge of BI in banking, database and ETL tools training
- Offer consulting services for Bank of Communications
- Data migrate & analysis & maintain for Bank of Communications

#### Education

## **Bachelor of Science (Computing) in Software Engineering**

Curtin University - Perth WA

August 2014 to December 2018

### Skills

- Python (2 years)
- Django (1 year)
- PyxII (Less than 1 year)
- Node js (2 years)
- React (2 years)
- Java (2 years)
- Docker (1 year)
- Deck.gl (2 years)
- Html (2 years)
- Css (2 years)
- JS (2 years)
- Git (2 years)

# Links

https://chen-bbe.github.io/MyPage/

https://github.com/Chen-BBe/

## Certifications and Licenses

# **SCJP**

2010 to 2012

Sun Certified Java Programmer

# Additional Information

• Language: Mandarin and English